for another shot and now we going back
to bed is she wanted to Dan she like
Yeah
tomorrow's hi everybody it's aleso here
and it's Nate Smith we're going to take
you behind the song of I like it she
another sh and now we going back to bed
I is Sheed to dance she like again you
really want to get your night going have
a good time you know you put this song
on you do it just feels like there's no
way you can listen to it not like want
to party I've been missing kind of like
when you go to a club you hear a song
that's more upbeat that's what I've been
missing and it's my favorite style too
of pop music I think it's just where I
feel like I belong in making that music
and it's got a little bit of that
nostalgic um 2000s kind of dance thing
about it and I think that's what's so
refreshing cuz we we've been missing
that I think again I don't know why it's
it's changed but to hear that come back
again it it gives me those like dulo all
that that world of those kind of s i
loved so much during that era back in a
fresh and modern way with country music
mixed in I think it's amazing I think
people are going to really freak out
over this one we set have to make the
song of the summer man and I can't
believe you're willing to do it so yeah
yeah it's been the easiest process it's
been so much fun you know going back and
forth with working on the record too has
been just Joy I think it's one of the
fastest songs I've ever worked on like
from the start of an idea to sitting
here today and having the song within
like 2 months I think you know so I cut
a vocal on it within a week yeah once we
had it was just like oh sounds perfect I
didn't have barely had any notes you
know I was like uh I don't think I even
had it was just sounding amazing build
everything around the vocal right so um
I went in um and and laid all my vocals
down and have a kind of specific process
with doing that and everything I want
every word and every line to be special
so it's it's really a line by line kind
of a a process um until it feels right
like you hear it and then you just kind
of go like ah it sounds like a record
you know for sure and you know when you
write the lyrics on a dance record you
kind of want to in my world I want to
keep it simple I want it to be very
direct very like Global as well you know
I I feel like people from all over the
world are going to understand this song
it's not that complicated but it's a lot
of fun and it's like like I said
straight to the point the combination
also of dance music and Country and big
vocal performers really works well it
feels like an Anthem so and that's that
was the goal yeah I'm always been a fan
of country
combined with dance music you know aich
was definitely one of the first one to
do it and since then you know everyone
realized oh my God this such a good
combination I was missing that kind of
record in my sets and also right now on
the radio we feel like we we we need
some bangers um not saying there's not
out there but I'm I'm just that specific
one that has the high energy higher BPM
straight to the porn guitar the humming
part and all that stuff combining that
kind dance it
[Music]
works the song started off at first uh
just the guitar and that was to kind of
like set the tone of the record like oh
without the thing yeah yeah so the first
time was just the guitars and then the
chorus came in but we changed that later
but so yeah it was this guitars
just sets the tone right away we're here
to have a good
time that's what it sounds like and then
later into the making of this song I
pull up to his trailer in where were we
in Minneapolis I think we're Minneapolis
and I said I think we should start the
song differently I think we should start
with his we call it humming part Game
Changer it was a game changer cuz you
were on the fence about it I we're going
back and forth cuz the guitars are
really really dope and there through the
entire song but uh you know when you
play the song you want instantly be like
oh what is that and I felt we got a
better reaction to that by using Nate's
vocal right away in the beginning so
no-brainer so here we
[Music]
go yeah it was so obvious that that was
the right decision because it like he
said it was good with just the guitars
but now it's special and it reinforces
that hook because that hook is really
catchy and really amazing and so you
have it early on like that cuz we're
going into the chorus right away pretty
much but to hear that hook you recognize
it again later in the song and you can
sing along with it so I think it was
really smart on your end to do that
should never wait too long for one of
the best parts of the song you
[Music]
know to keep building it up without
adding too much before the drop or the
chorus with everything on added this Tom
and intro kick I call it so smart D I
love that for
Vibe it just fit perfectly with the
guitar
[Music]
[Applause]
too I try to
balance your world with my world and I
feel like this intri is of like your
world and then when we go into the drop
we going into more of the dance
[Music]
elements we got a lot of stuff going on
we
got the low kick the top kick very
important in uh pop music I think that
you hear the top kick I feel like if you
don't really have a top kick uh it could
drown in the mix so I always feel like I
always add a top kick even if it barely
needs it just a little
bit
so and then we got some
snares it's um combined with a clap
here and gives that heavy hit heavy
snare like I said it's a lot of stuff
going on here so you really have to
balance you know these elements and and
and so nothing
drowns some
basic high
hats and of course the electronic base
that drives the song in the beginning
the Basse wasn't going like this it was
following this rhythm
so we'll
go in the first demo but uh I noticed
that having the Bas just going on the
one all the time uh gave it a nicer flow
so almost hits harder
yeah instead
of a lot of side chaining you know in
dance music we love that stuff we side
chain everything almost to get that
[Music]
pump the little ahas yeah those are
dope they're important they're like the
small little thing but no but they L
yeah they definitely fill out uh the
verse part I try to fill out fill out
like small gaps and make it more fun um
and we've done some here oops
so together with the vocals it kind of
fills out those small gaps to keep the
energy going CU I think you know the
more we listen to the song we never want
to lose momentum and and and building
and building so with Nate's vocal
here I mean I'm always moving around
quite a bit during my own shows and
everything but this one's just like like
a country music you don't see you don't
see a lot of the
and I love that I'm like why aren't we
doing that like in country because it's
a party but like seeing that happen it's
pretty amazing to see a whole SE of
people just going what the f vocal
production is so interesting to me yeah
how it goes together like the throws
versus the doubles versus the harmony
versus just just a verb throw like I'll
just go through this second time the
Core is coming so we obviously got the
main lead
[Music]
here got some doubles
I love this one oh yeah I do the high
[Music]
Oney what really makes the core strong
all these layers you know if I would
mute all this you would feel like
something was missing specifically for
the second time it comes in because
there's so much going on so you need a
lot to push everything up through the
mix the game also make this
[Music]
thing giv that football stadium feeling
that everyone is singing it together you
know what part I love so much that you
did on here too is when you told me that
because there's a part I was like the
violin's really cool that and he's like
no their horns like this part
the way that sounds on the track is
[Music]
insane yeah and it's the same thing
there you know adding stuff to a song
where a lot of stuff is happening it's
high energy fast BPM you know everything
going like there's certain things you
like you don't want to add because it
could just make it sound terrible you
know or just too much
everywhere in
[Music]
well there's a line that that that stood
out to me that was really country was uh
now she got her hands up on my Levis I
mean that's that's that's that's not a
pop lyric at all and stuff so that
really connected and resonated with me
and stuff are you wearing Levis now I'm
actually not wearing Levis but I'd say
nine out of 10 days I'm wearing Levis
you know I never wear Levis I don't know
you can go into the second
verse now she got her hands up on
well I guess we kind of have a little
precourse right here I forgot about this
part you really want to try not to make
people sick of the chorus until the song
is finished you know so you always got
to play a little bit of math here and
there figuring like okay how do we bring
back the chorus again without it not
being too obvious and like oh I kind of
knew that this was coming in again and
um we stripped everything down added a
preor
that's very simple and give that last I
would call it like Arena feeling mhm I
like it like with the chorus just the
guitar one of the guitars uh to give it
the fin final final
moment not to the chorus to the hook
thing exactly I love that you did that
cuz you think cor's right there for sure
exactly I have a little Theory you know
if you're going to bring back the chorus
one last time it needs to feel like it
really belongs there you know not just
do it because it's the like obvious
thing to do and it ends on that that
hookie thing so then when it starts
again it's like yeah it could go on Loop
forever it could
[Music]
loop I like