hi I'm Taylor Tomlinson and I'm going to
take you through my camera
roll okay so this is the first
photo it is a photo I took on my TV at
home of the day my last special have it
all came out on Netflix and it was
number one in TV shows for I think like
a day or two I knew it wasn't going to
be there for long so I said we better
take a photo of this while it lasts cuz
that was very cool I love being on lists
lists are really important to me anytime
I get to be on a list I try to capture
that moment this special was different
from the others for me because all my
dreams had come true professionally and
I think the first special quarter life
is like me trying to get to where I am
now look at you is me sort of in the
middle going is this going to go away
was this a fluke and have it all is me
really going yeah I'm I think I'm a real
comedian now I think I did it I think I
did what I set out to do which is really
nice have you guys introduced people you
were dating to your parents it's not
about introducing people you love to one
another is it no it's about showing your
partner why you're mean to them
sometimes
okay this is the second photo okay so
this is a photo of me on tour with Conan
O'Brien there was a day in Chicago I
believe there's an American girl I think
the original American Girl doll store is
in Chicago we were talking about
American Girls when I was on the standup
tour with Conan and I had had over
shared and said that I never got an
American Girl doll growing up that I
would just look through the catalog cuz
they're so expensive and then the next
day Conan's social team was like can you
come downstairs Conan's going to give
you a doll and he had me choose between
the Samantha doll and the kit doll and I
picked Samantha because I had read more
of her books growing up that's a that's
a little selfie of me and Sam I highly
recommend having one of your Idols give
you a doll it really helps on tough
days so stupid
okay next
photo okay so this photo was me last
year in London doing some shows and I
had never toured internationally before
which was really exciting I had never
seen Paddington before and my best
friend came with me to the first leg in
London and so we watched Paddington and
we're like this is the greatest movie
we've ever seen I would not shut up
about it and towards the end of the trip
my friend Dustin Nickerson who opens for
me bought me this Paddington Bear I'm
getting dolls from a lot of people in
this scrapbook I just realized he got me
a little Paddington to remember the trip
by and it made me very emotional and
then I took Paddington around to all of
the major landmarks and took photos of
them so this is one of them next
photo o this is me really living this is
me after I sold out two shows at Radio
City Music Hall which was absolutely
insane and beyond my wildest dreams and
Monday night we all went out and I think
we saw a show and then we went to a
Broadway Bar and you're not supposed to
take videos or photos so it feels very
free in there and someone on my team
just grabbed this real quick but this is
me drunk for the very first time in my
whole life and I really had a great time
look I'm not advocating for abstinence
but I'm glad I waited until I was 29 and
successful to get wasted at a Broadway
Bar it was the right way to go I was
drinking whatever my social media
manager handed me I was like what's that
can I try it get me one I don't know
anything about alcohol I've been drunk
twice ever and I'm like is that good
I'll have
that okay this speaking of international
tour dates so I also got to perform in
Australia last year for the first time
which was incredible and when I came
back the jet lag was unimaginable it was
terrible and I sort of lost my mind a
little bit I had given myself a few
weeks off and thought I'll rest and then
I couldn't because I was so tired so I
couldn't sleep I was really wired and I
also got weirdly insecure about the fact
that I had no hobbies to turn to when I
had time off on the plane ride back from
Australia I went down a rabbit hole on
Tik Tok watching people decorate cakes
and I thought if I get all the tools
surely I can decorate cakes it's not
that hard you just need all the tools
and I have money so I went and got a
bunch of tools and what you see here is
me trying to decorate a cake we put the
beginning stage ages in because it just
goes downhill from here it's really not
good there's a whole miniseries on my
Instagram of me trying to decorate these
cakes at home and it's pretty sad it
never goes well but people seem to find
it entertaining so unfortunately my only
hobby is still creating content and not
actually making anything anyone would
want to eat or look at then I put some
pink sprinkles on it I don't know if I
should do more sprinkles it lasted Maybe
two weeks and people still bring it up
to me they're like what happened to that
cake show I was like that was 2 weeks
that wasn't that didn't last that long I
think I only made like four cakes that
was a dark period next
one oh this is me being told by stepen
coar that I got the job hosting after
midnight I was on my way out and I got a
text from my team that was like can you
hop on a zoom with coar and everyone I
think they have a few more questions for
you because I was up for the job and I
had done the screen test the week before
and I thought oh yeah sure that's fine
and I got on and he sort of acted like
he was going to keep interviewing me
he's like there's a couple things I
didn't ask you and I was like okay and
then he totally faked me out and gave me
the job and this is my genuine and
sincere surprise I was so excited I was
so afraid it's crazy that this was only
in November this wasn't that long ago
and I feel so different than I did in
this picture picture I don't feel
differently about getting the job I just
feel different as a person as a result
of having this job and my life is very
different now it's funny to look back at
moments in your life knowing how much it
changed after that I'm really glad
somebody screenshot it on the call which
I really appreciated cuz they're like
you'll probably want to have this and I
do this is a photo of me at after
midnight in an outfit I really really
loved I'm so stupid when I got this job
I thought I was going to have to dress
myself so I like went out and bought
suits and I got there and they're like
you're so cute just we'll put these over
here we have a professional when I
started doing the show I was like can I
just wear the same suit every night like
the guys do and they're like you really
can't and I was like okay and then I
thought about it and I remember watching
Chelsea Lately and being a teenager and
being like ooh yellow tank top like I do
remember noticing her outfits like oh my
gosh her hair's up like I do remember
that stuff granted Chelsea antlers much
hotter than me so
okay this is my younger sibling and I
watching after midnight in my hotel room
which was the first time I'd watched the
show like I'd only seen Clips really
online or like on links that they'd sent
me I'd never actually watched it on TV
or even like Paramount plus and it was
so crazy to watch it on TV and go like
oh my gosh we filmed that yesterday now
it's just out there and it's happening
and it reminded me of watching like
Whose Line Is It Anyway when I was a kid
it really hit me and I was like oh this
is like a fun goofy silly show it just
felt very nostalgic to me so that also
felt significant my siblings and I are
really really close and they're so
lovely and supportive and think it's
cool but also know that I'm a loser
which is the perfect balance and exactly
what you need in your life if you're
going to be in Show Business people
going that's cool also you know simmer
down like
okay this is is a photo of me in front
of the Winter Garden theater where they
were doing the music man with Hugh
Jackman's signed glove that I really did
bid on and purchase in a charity auction
after the show people asked me if that
story from have it all is true that
picture is my proof that it actually is
and I do remember participating in the
auction it's very exciting have you ever
participated in an auction like one
where people are excited it was
thrilling and then it's over so fast and
you spent so much money but again is for
charity I would never just do an auction
for nothing and I got this glove for my
manager and there was also Sutton Foster
also signed a glove which I almost kept
but I was like no you got these for Judy
after this happened the very next night
I had a show at Town Hall in New York
and I did the first version of that bit
super worth it super worth it definitely
got my money's worth out of that glove
and then last
one this is me at 16 years old doing
standup somewhere that looks illegal I
don't even know where this was I don't
know if it's upstairs upstairs where a
business an apartment a hotel who knows
where this was but I do like this photo
because it shows you how far I've come
career-wise and acne wise anybody who's
made it in this business in the way they
want to it is important to remember how
far you've come and how hard it was to
get there and nothing drives that Point
home more than this photo for me and I
look how excited I
am I loved comedy so much and I still do
and that's who's doing stand up every
night inside me is this right here
[Music]